<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Whirling Science</title><link>http://thewhirlingscience.github.io/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://thewhirlingscience.github.io/feeds/gioele-la-manno.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><item><title>First Post</title><link>http://thewhirlingscience.github.io/blog/2015/12/28/first-post/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The website is under construction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a simple test of a post. 
I thank you for your visit and I invite you to come back in the future when the blog will be ready.
You will hopefully find a more developed website already on February 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this website is to offer "bits" of science reflections from different fields of natural science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below for you delightment and to the more practical purpose of testing the posting layout with a lon post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quotes are copy-pasted from &lt;a href="https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Galileo_Galilei"&gt;Wikiquote-Galilei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some years ago, as Your Serene Highness well knows, I discovered in the heavens many things that had not been seen before our own age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The passage of time has revealed to everyone the truths that I previously set forth; and, together with the truth of the facts, there has come to light the great difference in attitude between those who simply and dispassionately refused to admit the discoveries to be true, and those who combined with their incredulity some reckless passion of their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature … is inexorable and immutable; she never transgresses the laws imposed upon her, or cares a whit whether her abstruse reasons and methods of operation are understandable to men.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Gioele La Manno</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:thewhirlingscience.github.io,2015-12-28:blog/2015/12/28/first-post/</guid><category>Test</category><category>First</category><category>Galileo</category></item></channel></rss>